<item>
<title>Episode 1 - Checking In</title
<link>http://vidspot.net/tvizniqh6au3</link>
<thumbnail>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/a/a2/American_Horror_Story_Hotel_Teaser.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://40.media.tumblr.com/b9b50f185a14532f4de78c3217bec56b/tumblr_inline_nvt7c34NUW1td8azs_1280.jpg</fanart>
<info>Two Swedish tourists check in to the Hotel Cortez in downtown Los Angeles. They are attacked by a disfigured creature who was inside their room's mattress. Iris (Kathy Bates), the manager of the hotel, moves them to Room 64. Meanwhile, Detective John Lowe (Wes Bentley) is investigating the torture-murder of a couple. During his investigation, John receives a strange phone call telling him to go to the hotel where he will find a clue. At the Cortez, John falls asleep and wakes up with a vision of his missing son Holden (Lennon Henry). Heroin addict Gabriel (Max Greenfield) checks in and is violently raped by the Addiction Demon; before Gabriel dies, Hypodermic Sally (Sarah Paulson) appears and asks him to tell her that he loves her. Elizabeth (Lady Gaga) and Donovan (Matt Bomer) have a foursome with a couple they met. During sex, they slit the couple's throats and savor their blood. Will Drake (Cheyenne Jackson), the new hotel owner, arrives with his son Lachlan (Lyric Lennon). In a flashback to 1994, Sally and Donovan check in to the Cortez. Iris knocks on their door and argues with Sally for drugging her son. When Sally leaves disoriented, Iris shoves her out a window to her death. John Lowe arrives at the hotel with his luggage, and checks in to Room 64.</info>
</item>

<item>
<title>Episode 2 - Chutes and Ladders</title
<link>http://vidspot.net/csymzs5d3tiv</link>
<thumbnail>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/a/a2/American_Horror_Story_Hotel_Teaser.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://40.media.tumblr.com/b9b50f185a14532f4de78c3217bec56b/tumblr_inline_nvt7c34NUW1td8azs_1280.jpg</fanart>
<info>Will hosts a fashion show in the hotel lobby with the help of Vogue editor Claudia Bankson (Naomi Campbell). Model and actor Tristan Duffy (Finn Wittrock), a drug addict and narcissist, stars in the show. He meets Elizabeth, who turns him into a vampire and the two engage in a sexual relationship. Donovan discovers them and becomes jealous, resulting in Elizabeth ending their relationship. John goes to arrest Iris, but she instead tells him about the hotel through flashbacks. The sadistic James Patrick March (Evan Peters) built the hotel in the 1920s as a place for him to torture and murder people. Eventually police find him, so he and his loyal laundress Miss Evers (Mare Winningham) commit suicide. Meanwhile Lachlan and Scarlett develop a friendship, and Lachlan shows her a room with an empty indoor pool that contains four small coffins for Elizabeth's children. Scarlett recognizes her brother, Holden, in one of the coffins and returns to the hotel the next day to talk to him. She takes a photo of herself with him to prove to her parents that he is still alive; when John looks at the photo, Holden is blurry.</info>
</item>
